[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢大家
Welcome everybody.
欢迎各位的到来
Good morning.
早上好
It's early.
现在时间还早
I hope you had your coffee.
我希望你们已经喝过了咖啡
We have a lot to talk about
因为我们今天会有许多要谈的
today.
事情
Welcome to what's new in
欢迎来到
HomeKit.
“HomeKit 有什么新内容”
In iOS 11, watchOS 4 and tvvOS
在 iOS 11  watchOS 4 和
11.
tvOS 11 中
We have a ton of great features
今天我们将会提到
and enhancements we'd like to
非常多的优秀功能
talk to you today about.
以及增强功能
First, we will be providing an
首先 我们将总览一下
overview of HomeKit as a
HomeKit
framework.
这个框架
Second, we're going to be
之后 我们将会谈到
talking about some of the
一些在 iOS 11
updates and enhancements to the
对 HomeKit 框架的
HomeKit framework in iOS 11.
升级和增强
And Praveen will be sharing some
然后 Praveen 将会分享一些
exciting news about our
关于配件生态系统的
accessory ecosystem.
令人激动的新内容
The HomeKit framework allows
HomeKit 框架让你可以
your apps to easily set up and
轻松设置并控制
control your HomeKit
你的 HomeKit
accessories.
配件
HomeKit provides a central store
HomeKit 提供了一项中央存储
for the configuration of your
用来配置你的住宅
home, including rooms,
包括房间
accessories, automations and
配件 智能家居
more.
以及更多的东西
This configuration is
这项配置
synchronized across all of your
是在你的所有 App 和设备上
apps and devices.
同步进行的
And HomeKit is deeply integrated
而且 HomeKit 是深度集成在
in iOS, Watch OS and TV OS.
iOS  watchOS 和 tvOS 中的
You can control your accessories
你可以直接通过你的声音
and scenes directly with your
使用 Siri 或者
voice, using Siri, or using the
使用 Home App
Home app, you can control all of
来控制你的配件和场景
your accessories from any of
你可以通过任何一个你的设备
your devices.
来控制你的所有配件
And with just a swipe and a tap,
仅仅通过轻轻的滑动和点按
you can control your favorite
你就可以从控制中心
scenes and accessories right
控制你最喜欢的
from Control Center, and it has
场景和配件
really never been easier for you
对你而言 控制住宅从来没有
to control your home.
如此轻松过
And with an Apple TV or iPad as
通过 把 Apple TV 或者
your Home Hub, you can control
iPad 作为 Home Hub
your accessories from just about
你可以从世界上任何地方
anywhere in the world.
来控制你的配件
And we are happy to say that in
而且我们非常开心的宣布
addition to being a fantastic
除了作为一个优秀的扬声器
speaker, the Home Pod will also
Home Pod 将同样在今年晚些时候
be added as a Home Hub later
加入到 Home Hub
this year.
的行列中
And with a compatible home hub,
有了一个兼容性良好的 Home Hub
your home can be automated via
你的住宅可以通过基于时间和事件
time and event-based triggers.
的触发器来实现自动控制
And with over 70 accessory
随着超过 70 家的
manufacturers, either bringing
配件生产商
accessories to market or already
将新配件带入市场
have accessories on the market,
或者是已经有配件发布
the number of HomeKit
HomeKit 配件的数量
accessories continues to grow
将继续实现
month over month.
逐月的增长
It is super exciting.
这非常令人激动
We have a number of new features
我们有许多 iOS 11 新功能
to talk about in iOS 11 and
值得探讨
today we are going to focus on
今天我们将要重点关注
event triggers.
时间触发器
Today, I'm happy to say that we
今天 我可以开心的宣布
are introducing New Events, New
我们将要引入新的事件
Conditions, support for End
新的条件 对中断事件的支持
Events, and Recurrences.
以及事件重现
And finally we are talking about
然后 最终我们将谈到
the enhancement for Mutable
对可变事件的
Events.
增强功能
But before we dive into what is
但是在我们提到新内容之前
new, I'd like to do a quick
我想要快速地总结一下
overview of Event Triggers.
事件触发器
Event Triggers center around
事件触发器以事件
events.
为中心
When an event fires, it
当一个事件发生时
activates a trigger, and you can
它将激活一个触发器
have one or more events
同时你可以有一个或者多个事件
associated to an event trigger.
和一个事件触发器产生联系
We support two different types
我们现在支持两种
of events today.
不同类型的事件
The first, when the state of an
第一种 当一个配件的状态
accessory changes, such as
发生变化时 例如
opening of a door, or turning on
打开了一扇门或者
a light.
打开了一盏灯
Second, we support when a device
第二种 我们支持一个设备
enters or leaves a geo region.
进入或者离开一个地理区域
And when an event fires, and the
当一个事件发生
event trigger activates, it
事件触发器激活
executes one or more scenes.
它将执行一个或者多个场景
And a scene is comprised of one
而一个场景由一个
or more actions, such as
或者多个动作组成
unlocking my door, or turning on
例如解锁我的门
my lights.
或者打开我的灯
And you can gate the execution
而且当一个触发器通过
of a scene when a trigger is
条件被激活时
activated via conditions.
你可以得知场景的执行
And we support a number of
同时我们支持许多
different types of conditions.
不同类型的条件
First, based on the current
第一种是基于
time.
当前的时间
Second, based on the current
第二种是基于
state of an accessory.
当前配件的状态
Excuse me.
抱歉
And last, based on the relative
最后一种是基于
time to significant events, such
相对重要事件的事件
as sunrise and sunset.
例如日出和日落
Now, as an example, When we
现在举一个例子
arrive home and we open our
当我回到家的时候我打开了门
door, and in this case, opening
在这种情况下
the door is our event.
开门就是我们的事件
And after dark, this is our
天黑了
condition.
这就是我们的条件
And it is based on a significant
而这是基于日落
event of sunset.
这种重要事件
We want to say execute our
我们想要执行我们的
arrive home scene.
到家场景
And that is an event trigger.
那就是一个事件触发器
And we have a number of
我们还有很多
enhancements and new features
对事件触发器的增强功能
for event triggers.
以及新功能
The first of which is support
第一个是通过
for date-based events, via
HMCalendarEvent 来支持
HMCalendarEvent.
基于数据的事件
This provides an improved
这提供了超越 HM 时间触发器
scheduling capability over HM
的一种增强的
timer triggers.
计划能力
You can now take advantage of
现在你能够利用
all the features of the
这个触发器的所有功能
triggers, such as conditions,
例如条件
and some of the other features
还有一些其他的功能
we are going to be talking about
我们稍后将会
shortly.
谈到
And we support dates based on
同时我们支持
year, month, day, and hour
基于年份 月份 日期
minute combination.
以及小时与分钟结合的数据
Now, as an example, let's go
比如
ahead and create an event
让我们创造一个
trigger which executes at 5:30
每天下午 5:30 执行的
p.m. every day.
事件触发器
First, we are going to create
首先我们打算
our date component.
创建我们的日期成分
In this case, we are going to
在这个例子中
set two properties, the hour
我们将要设置两个属性
property to 17, indicates 5:00
小时属性设置为 17 表示下午 5：00
p.m. Second, we are going to set
然后我们将
the minute property to 30, and
分钟属性设置为 30
this indicates 30 minutes after
这指明了下午 5：00
5:00 p.m. We then simply create
之后的 30 分钟
our HMCalendarEvent, and we
随后我们简单的创建我们的 HMCalendarEvent
specify our recently created
然后我们指定
date component.
最近创建的日期成分
Now, we have just created an
现在 我们刚刚创建了
event which will fire at 5:30
一个每天 5:30 发生
every day.
的事件
We then simply create our
然后我们创建我们的
HMEventTrigger, and we're going
HM 事件触发器
to give it a friendly name.
我们打算给它一个友好的名字
In this case, we are going to
在这个例子中
call it Every day at 5:30 p.m.,
我们打算称它为每天下午 5:30
and then we specify our
然后我们要指定我们的
collection of events.
事件集
In this case, a single event,
在这个例子中是单独的一个事件
our HMCalendarEvent.
我们的 HMCalendarEvent
And now, in iOS 11, it is that
现在 在 iOS 11 中
easy to create event-based
非常容易创建基于
triggers based on times of the
具体时间和日期的
day or specific dates.
基于时间的触发器
We have also added support for
我们同时已经通过
significant time events, via
HMSignificantTimeEvent
HMSignificantTimeEvent.
添加了对重要时间事件的支持
This activates on significant
这会在重要事件发生时激活
events, such as sunrise, and
例如日出
sunset.
和日落
And we support a relative time
同时我们支持对
offset to these significant
这些重要事件的
events, both positive and
相对时间偏移
negative.
包括正偏移和负偏移
And this means you can schedule
而这意味着你可以
events to fire, say one hour
计划事件发生
after sunrise.
例如日出之后一小时
Now, let's go ahead and create
现在 让我们来
another event trigger.
创建另外一个事件触发器
This time, we want it to fire at
这次 我们要让它
sunrise every day.
在每天日出时触发
There we go.
来吧
First, we create our
首先 我们创建一个
HMSignificantTimeEvent, and we
我们的 HMSignificantTimeEvent
are going to specify sunrise as
然后我们将指定日出为
our significant event.
我们的重要事件
And we also specify our offset
同时我们指定
to be nil.
偏移为 0
Now, this indicates that we want
现在 这意味着
our event to fire at sunrise,
我们想让事件在日出时触发
not before, and not after.
不在这之前也不在这之后
We then simply create our
然后我们创建
HMEventTrigger, same as we did
我们的 HMSignificantTimeEvent
before, and we specify this time
就和我们之前做的一样
our sunrise event as a single
然后我们指定我们的这次日出事件
firing event.
为一次性触发事件
We've also added a convenience
我们同时在 iOS 上添加了
to iOS 11 to allow you to easily
方便的功能来让你
create a condition which is
更容易的创建一个在
between two significant events,
两次重要事件之间的情况
and note, that because these
需要注意的是
take significant events, they
因为这些需要依靠一些重要事件
support a relative time offset.
因此它们支持一个相对时间的偏移
So, for instance, I can create a
例如
condition which gates the
我可以创建一个情况
execution of my scene from say
让我的场景在
one hour after sunset, to one
日落后一个小时开始执行
hour before sunrise.
一直到日出之前的一个小时
This is available on
这在 HMSignificantTimeEvent 上
HMEventTrigger via predicate for
通过对两次重要事件之间
evaluating trigger occurring
评估触发的判断
between significant events.
来完成
In iOS 11, we have also added
在 iOS 11 中 我们也添加了
support for creating a event
对创建另一类事件的支持
which executes when a
这种事件在一个特征值
characteristic value crosses a
超过阈值时
threshold value.
触发
Now, for example, we could
例如
execute when the temperature
我们可以让事件
rises above 76 degrees in our
在家中温度超过 76 度时
home.
触发
We could also execute when the
我们同样可以让事件
temperature drops below 68
在家中温度降低到 68 度以下时
degrees in our home.
触发
And finally, we could execute
最后 我们可以
when the temperature is between
让事件在家中温度
68 and say 76 degrees in our
处于 68 度和 76 度之间时
home.
触发
Now, let's go ahead and build an
现在让我们来
example.
创建一个示例
We want to create an event
我们想要创建一个事件
trigger which executes when the
在我们家中
temperature in our home rises
温度上升到 76 度时
above 76 degrees.
执行
To do this, we first create an
为了达到这个目标
HMNumberRange.
我们首先要创建一个 HMNumberRange
Now, note, HMNumberRange is what
现在需要注意的是
specifies our range between a
HMNumberRange 指定了
minimum and maximum value.
我们最小值和最大值之间的范围
And we have provided two
而我们提供了两个
convenience initializers for you
方便的初始化器
to create a range within a
来创建最小值和
minimum or a maximum value only.
最大值之间的范围
In this case, we are providing
在这个例子中
the minimum value to be 76.
我们让最小值设置为 76
And our maximum value in this
而我们的最大值
case is an arbitrary large
是一个随机的大数
number, let's say it is positive
让我们认为它是
infinity.
正无穷
We then create our HM
然后我们可以创建
Characteristic Threshold Range
我们的 HM 特征阈值
Event.
范围事件
And we specify our target
我们同时指定了
characteristic.
我们的目标特征
In this case, it is a
在这个例子中
temperature characteristic,
它是温度特征
which can be a temperature
它可以是一个温度传感器
sensor, or it can be a
或者可以是一个
thermostat.
恒温器
We then simply provide our
我们只需要提供
threshold range, which was our
我们的阈值范围
recently created range of 76
即最近创建的
degrees.
76 度的范围
We then, as we've done before,
然后和我们之前做过的一样
create our HMEventTrigger, and
创建我们的 HMEventTrigger
this time, we specify our single
这一次 我们指定
firing event, which is our
一次性触发事件为
characteristic threshold range
我们的特征阈值范围
event.
事件
There we go.
来吧
Now, the state of our homes are
现在 我们住宅的状态
often tied to whether or not
经常与用户是否
users are in or out of the home.
在家中关联起来
For instance, I don't like to
例如
run my air conditioning or have
我不希望在家中没人的时候
lights on in my home when no one
让我的空调开着
is home.
或者让灯亮着
I am happy to say that in iOS
我可以开心的宣布
11, this is now supported via
在 iOS 11 中
HMPresenceEvent [applause].
HMPresenceEvent 已经支持了这项功能 [掌声]
It is super cool.
这非常的酷炫
You are going to love it.
你一定会爱上它的
We support a number of different
我们支持了许多
types of events.
不同类型的事件
Excuse me.
原谅我
There we go.
让我们继续
First, when the current user,
首先当前的用户
that is the device that we are
即我们提到的设备
talking about, arrives home.
到家时
On the other hand, we can also
另一方面 我们也可以
support when the current user
在当前用户离开家时
leaves home.
提供支持
Now, these two replace, or don't
现在无论它们
replace, but they augment
是否取代了之前的
HMLocationEvents, but instead of
它们都增强了 HMLocationEvents
tracking a single device, they
然而它们不依靠追踪一个单独的设备
now track a user.
它们追踪的是一个用户
We've also added support for
我们同样增加了对住宅中
multiple users of the home, in
多个用户的支持
fact, all users of the home.
事实上 是所有家庭中的用户
For instance, we support when
例如 我们支持
the last user leaves home.
当最后一个用户离开住宅时
Now note, this indicates that
现在注意
your home is now unoccupied.
这意味着你的住宅是无人占据的
It is a good time to do things
这就是做一些事情的好时机
such as turn off the lights,
比如关掉所有的灯
turn down the air conditioning,
关掉空调
even lock the doors.
甚至锁住门
And finally, of course, we
最后 当然
support when the first user
我们也支持当第一个用户
arrives home.
到家的情况
And this indicates that your
这意味着你的住宅
home is now occupied, and in
现在有人占用了
this case, it may be good for
在这种情况下
you to do things like turn down
也许你会想要做一些事情
the air conditioning, turn on
例如打开空调
some lights, unlock the doors.
打开灯光和解锁门
Now, let's go ahead and build
现在 让我们继续来
this last example, where we
完成最后一个例子
create an event trigger which
这里我们创建一个事件触发器
executes when the first user
它会在第一个用户到家时
arrives home.
执行
First, we create our
首先
HMPresenceEvent, and we are
我们创建我们的 HMPresenceEvent
going to specify our presence
同时我们将要指定我们的
type to be any user at home.
存在类型为任何一个用户在家时
Now, this indicates that we want
现在 这意味着
our event to fire when the first
我们想要让我们的事件在
user arrives home.
第一个用户到家时发生
We then, just as we have done
然后 正如我们之前
before, create an
做过的一样
HMEventTrigger, and we specify
创造一个 HMEventTrigger
our single firing event, in this
然后指定我们的一次性触发事件
case, which is our presence
在这个例子中
event.
这就是我们的存在事件
And you probably know what I am
你可能知道
going to say, but it really is
我打算说什么
that easy in iOS 11 to create
但是在 iOS 11 中基于自动控制
user presence based automations,
创造用户存在就时如此简单
and it is super cool, and we are
而且非常酷炫
super excited for you to try it
我们非常激动的想让你
out, and provide some enhanced
试一试 并为你的客户
features to your client, or your
或者你的 App 用户
app users, excuse me.
提供一些增强的功能 抱歉
Now, we didn't stop there.
我们并不满足于这样
We have also added support for
我们还添加了一些
user presence conditions.
为用户存在条件提供的支持
Now, for example, let's say that
例如 让我们假设
normally we want to execute our
我们想要在我们醒来时
good morning scene when we wake
或者当太阳升起时
up, or when the sun rises.
执行我们的早上好场景
But it doesn't make sense for us
但是如果没有人在家
to execute this if no one is
执行这个场景
home.
就是毫无意义的
In iOS 11, you can now gate the
在 iOS 11 中
execution of scenes based on
你可以通过基于用户存在条件
user presence via user presence
的用户存在
conditions.
来执行这些场景
This is available on
这些可以在 HM 事件触发器上
HMEventTrigger via predicate for
通过评估触发器 HM 事件触发器
evaluating trigger with
对存在的判断
presence.
来完成
And note that it takes a
请注意
presence event.
这需要一个存在事件
Now, let's go ahead and add a
现在 让我们继续
presence condition to our
在我们之前的日出事件触发器的基础上
previous sunrise event trigger
添加一个存在条件
and take a look at what it looks
并看一看它是
like.
什么样子的
First, we are going to create
首先 我们将创建一个
our significant time event,
我们的重要时间事件
which is our sunrise event,
也就是我们的日出事件
specifying no offset, same as we
指定这里没有偏移
did before.
如同我们之前做的一样
We then create our
然后我们创建一个
HMPresenceEvent, again same as
我们的 HMPresenceEvent
we did before, specifying any
也是和我们之前做的一样
user at home.
指定任何用户在家时
We then create our condition via
我们接下来通过 HM 事件触发器
HMEventTrigger, predicate for
创建条件进行
evaluating trigger with
评估触发器对
presence, and we specify our
存在的判断
presenceEvent.
并指定我们的存在事件
And then we create our
然后我们就可以创建
HMEventTrigger.
我们的 HMEventTrigger
Now, this time, we are going to
这一次我们将要
specify our condition as the
指定我们的条件为
predicate for the event trigger.
对时间触发器对判断
And now, and now we have just
我们刚刚创建了一个
created an event trigger which
事件触发器
will fire every day at sunrise,
它将在每天日出的时候启动
but will only execute the
但是只有在一个用户在家时
associated scenes when there is
才会执行相关的
a user at home.
场景
If you're like me, we often want
如果你和我一样
to execute a trigger, but only
我们通常想要执行一个触发器
temporarily.
但是只是暂时性的执行
For instance, when I open my
例如说 当我在晚上
patio door at night, I want my
打开一个院门
patio light to turn on, but
我想让我的院灯也点亮
after say 10 minutes, I want my
但是十分钟之后
patio light to turn off
我想让我的院灯
automatically.
自动熄灭
And this is now possible in iOS
这现在在 iOS 11 上
11 via EndEvents
通过 EndEvents 成为了可能
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
.
.
EndEvents are available on
EndEvents 可以在
HMEventTrigger, and they return
HM 事件触发器上启用
a collection of HMEvents.
它们会返回一个 HM 事件集
And you can update the existing
你可以对事件触发器更新
events or EndEvents for an event
这些存在的事件或者
trigger via update end events
通过 completionHandler 来
with completionHandler.
更新终止事件
Now, we have added a new event
现在我们为 EndEvents 添加了
for EndEvents.
一个新的事件
HMDurationEvent.
HMDurationEvent
This allows you to specify a
这允许你从
time interval from the trigger's
触发器的执行时间
execution time, at which point
在什么时候结束事件
to end the event.
来指定时间间隔
Now, on a similar note, we often
现在同样的
want a trigger to execute only
我们通常想要仅仅在
on certain days of the week, and
一周中的特定几天执行一个触发器
this is now possible via
现在通过 Recurrences
Recurrences.
这成为了可能
Recurrences are available on
Recurrences 可以在
HMEventTrigger, and they return
HMEventTrigger 上启用
an optional collection of date
它们会返回一个可选择的
components which specify the
数据成分集并指定了
days of the week for which the
一周中触发器活跃的
trigger is active.
日期
And you can update an existing
而且你可以通过
event trigger with new
使用 completionHandler 更新
occurrences via Update
来将存在的事件触发器
Recurrences with
更新为 Recurrences
completionHandler.
新的触发事件
Now, as an example, I like to
现在来举一个例子
get up just a little later on
我想要在周末的时候
the weekends, as I'm sure many
晚一点起床
of you do.
我相信你们中很多人也是一样的
So I don't want my Good Morning
所以我不想让
Scene to automatically execute
早上好场景在日出之后
an hour after sunrise.
一个小时就自动执行
Instead, I'd like to use Siri to
相反 我想使用 Siri
go ahead and say, "Good
并让它说
morning."
“早上好”
So let's go ahead and gate our
现在让我们继续
previous sunrise event trigger
把之前的日出事件触发器
to only execute during the week,
改成仅在周一到周五
Monday through Friday.
期间执行
To do this, we create our
为了达成这个目标
HMSignificantTimeEvent, same as
我们创建了一个 HMSignificantTimeEvent
we did before.
如同我们之前做过的一样
Then we create our collection of
然后我们创建了
DateComponents.
我们的数据成分集
We are going to call these
我们打算称它们为
weekdays, then for each day of
工作日 对于工作日的每一天
the week, Monday through Friday,
从周一到周五
we create a new DateComponent,
我们创建一个新的数据成分
and we specify the weekday
然后我们指定工作日属性为
property to be the current day
这一周的当前日期
of the week, then we simply add
然后我们将这个添加入
this to our weekdays collection.
我们的工作日集
And then when we create our
然后我们创建了
HmeventTrigger, we specify our
HM 事件触发器
collection of recurrences, which
我们指定了重复事件集
are date components, as
即日期成分
recurrences are of our
因为重复事件是我们的 EventTrigger
EventTrigger.
的一部分
And this allows us to restrict
这允许我们基于
the execution of event triggers
每周的日期
based on the day of the week.
来限制事件触发器的执行
But furthermore, we also
但是进一步来说
sometimes want to create an
我们有时也想创建一个
event trigger which only
仅仅执行一次的
executes once, and then auto
事件触发器
disables itself.
然后让它自动失效
This is now possible via Execute
现在这通过 ExecuteOnce
Once.
成为了可能
As an example, you may want to
例如
create an event trigger that
你也许想创建一个在明天日落时
executes tomorrow at sunset, but
执行的事件触发器
you don't want it to repeat.
但是你不想让它重复执行
It is a great feature, and we
这是一个非常好的功能
are excited for you to try it
我们非常兴奋的想让你
out.
去尝试一下
This is available on
这个功能
HMEventTrigger via the Execute
在 HM 事件触发器下的
Once property, and you can
ExecuteOnce 属性里
update an existing or new event
而且你可以通过使用 completionHandler
trigger to only execute one time
升级 ExecuteOnce 来将
via update executeOnce with
已经存在的事件或者新的事件触发器
completionHandler.
升级到只执行一次 completionHandler
The last, we've heard your
最后我们已经
feedback and we understand how
听说了你们的反馈
difficult it currently is to
我们理解当前将事件触发器中
update existing events on an
已经存在的事件升级
event trigger.
是非常困难的
Let's take an example.
让我们举一个例子
If you were building an app and
如果你在开发一个 App
updating a single event, you
并升级一个单独的事件
first had to copy the properties
你首先必须在应用中
of that event in your
复制那个事件的属性
application, then you had to
然后你必须
allow the user to modify that
允许用户来修改
event.
那个事件
Once the user completed their
一旦用户完成了他们的改变
changes, you had to create a
你必须使用新的属性来
brand new HMEvent with the new
创建一个全新的 HMEvent
properties then you had to
然后你必须
remove the existing event, via
通过 removeEvent
removeEvent with
和 completionHandler
completionHandler.
来删除已经存在的事件
And then add the new event via
然后通过 addEvent 以及 completionHandler
addEvent with completionHandler.
来添加新的事件
And this is a number of steps to
仅仅升级一个单独的事件
update just one single event.
就需要如此多的步骤
And so in iOS 11 we have made it
所以在 iOS 11 中
simpler via a single method
我们通过一个单独模式的
updateEvents with
updateEvents 和 completionHandler
completionHandler.
让事情变得简单了
Now this takes a collection of
这使用了一个 HM 事件集
HMEvents which represent the new
它代表了事件触发器的
events for an event trigger.
新事件
And we have also added support
我们也增加了
for all defined HMEvents for
对已经定义的 HMEvents 的
mutable copies.
可变副本的支持
So what does this mean?
所以这意味着什么呢
You can now simply take a
你现在可以仅仅使用
mutable copy of an existing
一个已经存在事件的
event, make any changes the user
可变副本
has requested, and then commit
作出任何用户要求的改变
those changes via updateOnce
然后使用 updateOnce 和 completionHandler
with completionHandler.
来实现这些改变
Let's go ahead and see an
让我们继续来看一个
example of updating our previous
将我们之前的日出事件触发器
sunrise event trigger to execute
升级到日出后 30 分钟执行的
30 minutes after sunrise.
例子
First, we get our existing
首先 我们有
HMEvent.
我们已经存在的 HMEvent
We are going to-this will return
我们打算 这将会
an object of type
返回一个 HMSignificantTimeEvent 类型的
HMSignificantTimeEvent.
对象
We then simply create a
然后我们创建一个
mutableCopy, which will return
可变副本 这将返回一个
an object of type
HMMutableSignificantTimeEvent 类型的
HMMutableSignificantTimeEvent.
对象
We can then update the offset of
然后我们可以通过
our sunrise event, by creating a
创建一个新的日期成分
new Date Component.
来升级我们的日出事件的时间偏移
We specify the minute property
我们指定分钟属性为 30
to 30, to indicated 30 minutes
来表示重要事件
after the significant event, and
之后的 30 分钟
then simply update the offset of
然后升级我们的 mutableSunriseEvent
our mutableSunriseEvent to our
到我们的新的
new date component.
日期成分
Now note, we haven't actually
请注意
changed our event trigger yet.
我们还没有真正改变我们的事件触发器
It will still execute at
它仍然会在日出的时候
sunrise.
执行
So move our event trigger to 30
所以为了把我们的事件触发器
minutes after sunrise, we simply
改变到日出后到 30 分钟
need to call UpdateEvents, with
我们只需要引用 UpdateEvents 函数
completionHandler, providing a
和 completionHandler 来提供
collection of new events.
新的事件集
In this case, we simply pass our
在这个例子中
single mutableSunriseEvent.
我们忽略掉单个 mutableSunriseEvent
And now in iOS 11, it is that
现在在 iOS 11 中
easy for your apps to update
把已经存在的事件
existing events on an
在 HMEventTrigger 上升级
HMEventTrigger.
对于你的 App 来说是非常容易的
We've covered a tone of new
我们已经谈到了一系列的
topics and enhancements to
新话题以及
HMEventTriggers.
对 HMEventTriggers 的功能增强
First, we have added support for
首先我们添加了
new events, supporting dates.
对新事件的支持 并支持了日期
Significant events,
重要事件
characteristic threshold range,
特征阈值范围
and user presence.
和用户存在
We have added new conditions,
我们已经增加了新的条件
supporting significant time
支持了重要时间范围
ranges and user presence.
以及用户存在
We have added support, excuse
我们增加了对终止事件的
me, for end events, which allow
支持
you to specify temporary event
这允许你来指定临时事件触发器
triggers which can
它可以在特定的
auto-deactivate after a
一段时间之后
specified amount of time.
被自动重复激活
We've added support for
我们也添加了对重复发生事件的支持
recurrences which allow you to
这允许你指定
specify when your event trigger
什么时候你的事件触发器
will be active and finally, we
是处于激活状态的
have added support for mutable
最后我们还增加了对
events for all defined event
所有已定义事件类型的可变事件的支持
types, which makes it easier for
这让你的 App 在 iOS 11 上
your applications in iOS 11 to
升级已经存在的 HMEventTriggers 时
update existing HMEventTriggers.
变得更加容易
And now, I'd like to hand it off
现在我想把时间交给 Praveen
to Praveen, to give you some
他将告诉你一些关于
exciting updates about our
我们的配件生态系统的
accessory ecosystem.
令人激动的升级
Praveen?
Praveen
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks Matt.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Matt
Good morning everyone.
大家早上好
My name is Praveen Chegondi, and
我的名字是 Praveen Chegondi
I am here to share with you new
我来这里是为了和你们分享
protocol features and
一些协议功能
enhancements that are in iOS 11.
以及在 iOS 11 上的增强功能
I have a few exciting topics to
今天我有一些令人激动的话题
talk about today.
来和你们分享
I am going to be sharing some
我将要分享一些
great news about what we are
关于我们对 HomeKit 配件协议规范
doing with the HomeKit accessory
做了些什么改变
protocol specification.
的好消息
I am also going to be talking
我同时打算谈一谈
about enhancement to the HomeKit
HomeKit 配件协议
accessory protocol.
的增强
Supportive new accessory
在 iOS 11 上
categories in iOS 11.
支持了新配件分类
Addition to the authentication
对 HomeKit 配件的认证过程
process for HomeKit accessories.
的添加
And finally, we will be rounding
最后
up with improvements to the
会谈到对我们的
self-certification process for
Mfi 执照者的自我认证过程
our MFi licensees.
的提高
Let's start off with a quick
让我们从 HomeKit
overview of the HomeKit
配件协议
Accessory Protocol
规范的概览
Specification.
开始谈起
The HomeKit Accessory Protocol
HomeKit 配件协议规范
Specification describes how a
描述了一个 Apple 设备作为控制器
controller, which is an Apple
是怎么样和一个配件
device, communicates with an
进行交互的
accessory, along with the
同时也包括了
security requirements.
一些安全要求
All sessions between Apple
所有 Apple 设备和配件之间
devices and accessories over
针对 HomeKit 的会话
HomeKit are end-to-end encrypted
都是端对端加密
and mutually authenticated.
并相互认证的
The specification provides
规则提供了一些双方
implementation details for both
的 IP 和蓝牙 LE 配件的
IP and Bluetooth LE accessories.
实现细节
And you can also get details on
你可以同样
how to describe each of the
从 HomeKit 支持的怎样描述
accessory categories that are
每个配件分类上得到
supported in HomeKit, such as a
这些细节
light bulb, fan, thermostat, and
例如灯泡 风扇 恒热器
many, many more.
还有更多的东西
For complete overview of the
想要关于 HomeKit 配件协议的
HomeKit accessory protocol, you
完整概览
can refer to the 2014 session,
你可以参考 2014 会议
Designing Accessories for iOS
为 iOS 和 OS X 设计
and OS X.
配件
Until now, the specification was
直到现在
available to MFi licensees,
规范已经可以在 Mfi 执照上找到了
whose accessories carried the
这些配件在完成自我认证之后
logo "works with Apple HomeKit"
会在上面印刻
after completing
“适配 Apple HomeKit”
self-certification.
的图标
Starting today, we are also
从今天开始
making a version of the HomeKit
我们正在努力
Accessory Protocol Specification
提供一版让每一个有开发者执照的人
available to anyone with a
都能使用的
developer license
HomeKit 配件协议规范
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So, if you are a student
所以 如果你是一个
developer, or even a hobbyist,
学生开发者或者业余爱好者
and want to learn about HomeKit
并且想要学习 HomeKit 协议
protocol and want to create
想要创建配件
accessories for your personal
作为私人用途
use, you can now do that
你现在可以这么做了
[applause].
[ 掌声 ]
The HomeKit developer page has
HomeKit 开发者页
been updated with the
已经对规范进行了更新
specification, and also you will
你也可以找到其他的
find other useful information,
有用信息
such as frequently asked
例如经常问到的问题
questions, and guidelines to
和对创建你自己的 HomeKit App
building your HomeKit apps.
的指导
Because the specification has
因为规范里面有
Apple's proprietary information,
Apple 的产权信息
you will need to agree to a
你需要同意
click-through license before
一项点按阅览执照
downloading it.
才能下载它
And with all this information,
有了这些信息
we are looking forward to seeing
我们期盼着看到
what new ideas you're going to
你们会带来一些
come up with.
什么样的新主意
And let's say you come up with a
让我们假设
really cool prototype?
你们会带来一些很酷炫的样板
And now, you want to develop a
现在 你想要开发
HomeKit accessory for commercial
一个 HomeKit 配件
sale.
以用于商业用途
You need to join the Apple MFi
你需要加入 Apple Mfi
Program.
项目
Program and go through
并通过
self-certification before you
自我认证
can begin your manufacturing or
才可以开始你的配件制造
sale of your accessories.
以及销售
And this is really exciting.
这非常令人激动
And I recommend that you check
而我建议你
the developer page often for the
经常查看开发者页
latest updates, as we continue
的最近更新
to introduce new features and
因为我们会持续的介绍一些
enhancements to the
新功能和对规范的
Specification.
增强
Talking about enhancements.
说到增强
In iOS 11, we made some great
在 iOS 11 中
enhancements to the HomeKit
我们对 HomeKit 配件协议
Accessory Protocol.
进行了一些大幅的改善
Now, let's see how a user with
现在让我们来看一看
iOS 10 sets up a HomeKit
一个 iOS 10 的用户是怎么样
Accessory, such as a light bulb.
设置一个 HomeKit 配件的 例如灯泡
These of course on the
这些当然就是配件
accessory, by putting the light
把灯泡放在插座上
bulb in the socket, chooses the
从 Home 中的添加配件选项
accessory from the add accessory
选中配件
option in the Home, and scans
然后扫描 8 位
the eight digit setup code.
设置代码
In three easy steps, the user is
通过简单的三步
able to set up a HomeKit
用户就能够设置一个
Accessory that is simple and
简单而有效的
great.
HomeKit 配件了
A couple of things to note in
这个过程中
this process.
需要注意一些事情
The accessory must be powered on
配件必须通电
for it to show up.
以让它出现
Secondly, the setup code is used
第二点 设置代码
for the initial HomeKit pairing
是仅仅用来初始化 HomeKit 配对的
only, and this is to ensure that
这是为了确保
you and only you are setting up
只有你才能设置
the accessory.
这个配件
For many accessories that are
对于很多安装在
installed in hard to reach
难以接触地方的配件
places, such as a light bulb, or
例如灯泡
have set up codes printed on the
或者将设置代码印在
back of the product, it makes it
产品的背面
difficult to scan the setup code
会让它通电之后
when it is powered on.
不容易扫描到设置代码
Or even choosing an accessory
或者甚至当你在
when you are setting up multiple
设置一个模型的多个
accessories of the same model
配件时选则一个
becomes challenging.
配件具有挑战性
In iOS 11, we are introducing
在 iOS 11 中
enhanced set of process to
我们引入了优化的一系列
further simplify accessory
过程来进一步简化配置
setup.
设置
With the enhanced setup, users
随着设置的优化
can now scan the setup code, and
用户现在可以扫描设置代码
then power on the accessory.
然后给配件通电
To achieve this, we are
为了达到这个目标
enhancing the setup payload to
我们正在增强设置的负载
include setup ID in addition to
使它在设置代码之外
the setup code.
额外包括设置 ID
iOS 11 uses the setup ID to
iOS 11 使用设置 ID
start the pairing process with
在设置代码扫描之后开始
the accessory when the setup
配件的配对过程
code is scanned, and matches to
然后在配件通电之后
the accessory when it is powered
使它配对到
on.
配件
It is that simple.
这非常容易
To deliver the enhanced setup
为了传递增强的设置代码
code, we are now supporting
我们现在支持
scanning of QR codes for setting
扫描二维码来
up HomeKit accessories
设置 HomeKit 配件
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
The QR code is standards based
二维码是一个基于标准的码
and can be as small as 10 by 10
并且可以小到 10mm
millimeters.
10 mm
That is pretty small.
这真是非常的小
The small form factor of the QR
二维码的小型化
code will help a lot of
会帮助很多制造商
manufacturers to put the QR code
来将二维码放到
on the smaller accessories, and
更小的配件上
this is really great.
这真是非常出色
But we didn't stop there.
但是我们没有在这里停下
We took one step further, and in
我们又朝前迈进了一步
addition to supporting QR code,
除了支持二维码之外
we also added support for NFC
我们还添加了对 NFC 标签的
tags.
支持
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; And we are really excited
&gt;&gt; 而我们对此
about this.
真的很兴奋
With NFC tags that are
有了和增强设置代码
programmed with the Enhanced
编程在一起对 NFC 标签
Setup Code, we can now deliver
我们现在可以传递
even more seamless user
甚至更多无缝的
experience for setting up
设置配件的
accessories.
用户体验
The user needs to just tap to
用户仅仅需要
pair and it is that simple, and
点按来配对
it is fantastic.
这非常简单而且美妙
The whole experience in setting
整个在 iOS 11 上
up accessories in iOS 11 with
设置配件的体验
the support of QR code or NFC
因为有了二维码
tag for HomeKit Accessories is
和 NFC 标签对 HomeKit 配件的支持
just fantastic.
变得非常美妙
Now, let's talk about Bluetooth.
现在让我们来谈一谈蓝牙
Over the last few years, we have
在过去的几年
seen an influx of Bluetooth LE
我们已经见过蓝牙 LE HomeKit 配件
HomeKit Accessories.
的兴起
This is because Bluetooth LE
这是因为蓝牙 LE 配件
Accessories offer a lot of
拥有很多的
advantages.
优势
They are small, they are
他们很小
extremely low power, and many
而且功耗极低
are battery operated, such as a
许多都是电池供电的
contact sensor, motion sensor,
例如接触感应器 动作感应器
and many more, and users use
以及其他更多
these to trigger events when a
用户使用它们在特定动作发生时
certain action takes place.
触发事件
And this is really great.
这真是极好的
Now, let's see how Bluetooth
现在让我们来看一看蓝牙通知
notifications work in iOS 10.
在 iOS 10 上是怎么工作的
In iOS 10, when an accessory
在 iOS 10 上
state changes, it triggers a
当配件状态变化的时候
state change notification.
它会触发一个状态改变通知
The home of apple TV in this
Apple TV 的 Home
case picks up the state change,
在这种情况下检测到状态变化
and then establishes a
然后建立了一个会话
communication, a secure
一个和配件之间的
communication with the accessory
安全会话
to determine what state has
来决定是什么状态发生了变化
changed, and then triggers the
然后触发
automation.
自动程序
The whole process results in a
整个过程会导致
few seconds of latency for the
几秒钟的停滞
automation to be executed.
来让自动程序执行
In iOS 11, we changed the
在 iOS 11 中
mechanism completely to
我们完全改变了机制
significantly reduce latency,
显著降低了延迟
and we are doing this by what we
而我们是通过
call Secure Broadcast Session to
运用安全广播通知会议发送通知
send the notification.
来达到这一目标的
Here, the iOS controller
在这里
configures the accessory with an
iOS 控制器使用加密的钥匙
encryption key, and the
来配置控制器
interested characteristics that
其中相关的特征
can be included in the secure
会被包括在
broadcast notifications.
安全广播通知中
Now, when a characteristic
现在 当一个特征发生改变时
changes, the accessory encrypts
配件加密了
the state change, and then sends
状态变化
a notification to the Home app,
然后给 Home App 发送了一个通知
which will then immediately
这会立即让自动程序
execute the automation.
运行起来
With this enhancement, we are
有了这个增强
seeing a number of accessories
我们可以看到许多的配件
where the latency has gone from
它们的事件触发时
a few seconds to under a second
延迟从原来的几秒
for the events to be triggered.
提升到少于一秒
And the best part about this
而关于这个增强的
enhancement is that you just
最好的部分是
need to upgrade to iOS 11 and
你仅仅需要升级到 iOS 11
get new form ware for your
就可以得到新的固件
accessories to ensure faster,
来让你的配件更快
because you don't need to buy
因为你不需要
new products
买新的产品
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
And with the new event triggers
随着 Matt 稍早提到的
Matt talked about earlier, and
新的事件触发器
with secure broadcast
还有对蓝牙 LE 配件的
notifications for Bluetooth LE
安全播报通知的出现
accessories, it's just
智能家居
incredible how home automation
将会被以不可思议的方式
is going to be defined now.
重新定义
Coming to accessory categories.
接着说配件分类
HomeKit supports a wide range of
HomeKit 支持广泛的
accessory types from sensors, to
配件类型
cameras and many more.
从传感器到相机以及更多
Every year, we continue to add
每一年我们继续
supportive new accessory
增加新的配件
categories.
分类
This year, in iOS 11, we are now
今年在 iOS 11 中
adding support for sprinklers
我们增加了洒水器
and faucets
和水龙头
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
With the support of sprinklers
随着 HomeKit 对
in HomeKit, users can now
洒水器的支持
control watering the garden by
用户现在可以通过 Siri
Siri.
给花园浇水了
Somewhat in a similar accessory
有一个相似的
category type, which is water
配件分类类型
related, let's talk about
也是和水相关的
faucets.
接着我们将谈谈水龙头
For many users, it is a daily
对于很多用户而言
ritual to turn on the shower,
打开淋浴是每天的一个仪式
let the water run, and wait for
让水流出
the water to turn to the right
等待水温变得正常
temperature before you get in
然后进入
the shower.
淋浴之中
Now, while having your morning
现在 当你在享用
cup of coffee, you can let Siri
你的早餐咖啡时
know it's bath time, and by the
你可以让 Siri 知道沐浴的时间
time you finish your cup of
当你享用完你的一杯咖啡
coffee, the water temperature is
水温已经
just right to your desired
到达了你所设置的温度
setting, and this can be
而这可以通过
achieved with the faucets
水龙头配件分类
accessory category.
来实现
That's pretty neat
这真是令人愉快
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Let's talk about authentication
现在让我们来谈一谈
now.
认证
At Apple, security and quality
在 Apple
is of utmost importance to us.
安全和质量对我们而言是最重要的
Our customers trust that their
我们的用户信任
accessories are tested
他们的配件是经过
thoroughly by MFi licenses and
MFi 执照测试并
audited by Apple.
受 Apple 审查的
To ensure accessories are
为了确保配件是
trusted and self-certified, we
受信赖的并且自我认证的
have adopted hardware-based
我们采用了基于硬件的
authentication.
认证方式
Starting with iOS 11, we are now
从 iOS 11 开始
introducing an alternate method
我们现在引入了一种
to authenticate HomeKit
替代方式来认证
Accessories.
HomeKit 配件
Now, accessories can be
现在配件
authenticated by software
可以通过软件来认证了
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
This provides a great option to
这提供了一个非常好的选择
enable HomeKit and shipping
来启用 HomeKit
accessories that can be upgraded
并运送可以升级到 HomeKit 的
to HomeKit.
配件
For our MFi licensees, we will
对于我们的 Mfi 执照来说
be sharing more information
我们稍后将分享更多的
about the implementation later.
关于安装的信息
Continuing on the topic of
继续我们关于配件质量的话题
accessory quality, we now have
我们现在有了新的
new and improved process and
升级的过程
tools to help MFi licensees
以及工具来帮助 Mfi 执照
access the launch of HomeKit
接入 HomeKit 配件的
Accessories.
启动
We now have automated tools to
我们现在有了自动化的工具
test your accessory and continue
来测试你的配件
to automate more and more test
并继续自动化进行
cases, and we urge all MFi
更多的测试
licensees to always get the
我们敬请所有的 Mfi 执照
latest tools before you begin
在你开始测试之前
your testing.
总最先使用最新的工具
Also, we are glad to announce
同时我们非常高兴的宣布
that we now have two Apple
我们现在有了两个
authorized third-party labs here
在美国的 Apple 授权的第三方
in the United States, and
实验室
authorizing more third-party
并且下个月
labs in China, and UK next
将授权更多的在中国
month.
和英国的第三方实验室
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; And this should help a lot of
&gt;&gt; 这将帮助很多
MFi licensees to launch the
Mfi 执照者更快的
accessories sooner.
启动配件
To recap the session, this year,
来总结一下
we introduced many compelling
今年我们介绍了很多
and useful HomeKit features.
有信服力并且有效的 HomeKit 功能
Matt talked about the great
Matt 谈到了
enhancements to event triggers,
对事件触发器的极好的优化
and introduced new APS you can
并且介绍了新的 APS
adopt in your apps to redefine
你可以应用到你的 App 中
home automation.
来重新定义智能家居
I shared news about HomeKit
我分享了一些关于
Accessory Protocol
HomeKit 配件协议规范对
Specifications being made
所有开发者可用的
available to all developers.
新消息
And enhanced accessory setup
并且谈到了改善的
process makes it even better
配件设置过程
than what it was before.
这使得它比以往更加便利
An interruption of secure
对于蓝牙 LE 配件的
broadcast notifications for
安全广播通告的中断
Bluetooth LE accessories will
将使得
make the event triggers go
事件触发器
faster.
更加快速
And introduced new accessory
并介绍了新的
categories, Sprinklers and
配件分类
Faucets.
洒水器和水龙头
And finally, we provided an
最后我们提供了
update on automation tools for
对自认证
self-certification and
自动化工具的升级
authorizing third party labs
并授权了全世界的
around the world to accelerate
第三方实验室
the launch of HomeKit
来加速开启
Accessories.
HomeKit 配件
We at Apple are really excited
我们在 Apple
about all these features, and we
真的为所有这些新功能感到激动
can't wait to see what you are
我们已经迫不及待的想看到
going to do with them.
你们是怎么使用它们的
A couple of important things
在我们结束这次会议之前
before we close the session.
还有一些重要的事情想跟你们说
We have two HomeKit labs for you
我们这周有两个为你们准备的
this week, where you can chat
HomeKit 实验室
with a number of HomeKit
在那里你可以和许多 HomeKit 工程师交谈
engineers, who will be happy to
他们将非常开心的为你解答
answer any questions that you
任何有关你的 App
have with regards to your apps
以及配件的
and/or accessories.
问题
We will also be demonstrating
我们也将解释
some of the new features and
我们刚刚谈到的
enhancements that we just talked
在 iOS 11 中加入的
about that are introduced in iOS
一些新功能以及
11.
增强功能
The first lab is right after
第一个实验室
this session in Technology Lab
在这次会议之后
J.
将在技术实验室 J 进行
Thank you very much for coming,
非常感谢你们的到来
and enjoy the rest of your
请享受你们接下来的
conference.
会议
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]